Guide to the Fred Eggan Papers 1870-1991
University of Chicago Library
- Series XII: Addendum
  - Subseries 7: Degrees, Awards and Honors
    - National Academy of Sciences- Medal and Rosette, 1963, 1965 (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - Pueblo of Zuni- Certificate of Appreciation (Posthumous), 1991 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 1)
    - American Anthropological Association, Distinguished Service Award, 1990 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 2)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Membership Certificate, 1963 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 3)
    - Society of the Sigma XI, Chicago Chapter, Membership Certificate, 1933 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 4)
    - American Philosophical Society- Certificate of Membership, 1962 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 5)
    - Royal Anthropological Institute- Diploma of Honorary Fellowship, 1962 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 6)
    - University of Chicago- M.A. Diploma, 1928 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 7)
    - University of Chicago- B.Phil. Diploma, 1927 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 8)
    - National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America- Diploma of Membership, 1963 (Box 186 [Oversize], Folder 9)
    - Woodblock Plaque- Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences- Fellowship, undated (Box 187)
  - Subseries 8: Photographs, Slides and Negatives
    - Sub-subseries 1: Photographic Prints
      - Photo Album- “Abra Tingajan”, undated (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Keys to Photographs/ Contact Strips, undated (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Philippines Contact Strips- Series A-D, undated (Box 188, Folder 3)
      - Philippines Contact Strips- Series E-H, undated (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Philippines Contact Strips- Series J-P, undated (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - Philippines Contact Strips- Series Q-U, undated (Box 188, Folder 6)
      - Philippines Contact Strips, Series V-Y, 1, 1B, 1C, 2A, 2E, undated (Box 188, Folder 7)
      - Philippines, Sagada- Contact Sheets, undated (Box 188, Folder 8)
      - Philippines- People, and Portrait of Pedro Lopos, 1950, undated (Box 188, Folder 9)
      - Philippines, Sagada- Prints, undated (Box 188, Folder 10)
      - Philippines- Photo #12 (Panorama)- Lubuagon, undated (Box 188, Folder 11)
      - Philippines- Various Photos, undated (Box 188, Folder 12)
      - Philippines- Various Photos, People, undated (Box 188, Folder 13)
      - Philippines- Sagada, Ricefields, undated (Box 188, Folder 14)
      - Philippines- Built Material Forms, Architecture, Manila Cityscape, undated (Box 188, Folder 15)
      - Philippines- Landscapes and people (Indoors and Outdoors), undated (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Philippines- Sagada, Mrs. Pedro Lopos and Family, 1956, undated (Box 189, Folder 2)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous Prints, undated (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - Philippines- St. Mary’s School Faculty, 1954-1955 (Box 189, Folder 4)
      - Philippines- People, undated (Box 189, Folder 5)
      - Philippines- Photo Post Cards, 1949-1950, undated (Box 189, Folder 6)
      - Yangkse River and Hong Kong Harbor, undated (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - Mindanao Photographs, undated (Box 189, Folder 8)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 189, Folder 9)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 189, Folder 10)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 189, Folder 11)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 189, Folder 12)
      - Philippines-Miscellaneous, undated (Box 189, Folder 13)
      - North Vietnam- 3 Tay Girls and Note, undated (Box 189, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 189, Folder 15)
      - Film Strips, Miscellaneous Films, undated (Box 189, Folder 16)
      - Film Strips, Miscellaneous Films, Key, undated (Box 189, Folder 17)
      - Philippines- Contact Strips, undated (Box 189, Folder 18)
      - Philippines- Sagada, undated (Box 190, Folder 1)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 190, Folder 2)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous Portraits, undated (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - Philippines- Parker Lake, S. Cotubata (Chapman?), 1935 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 190, Folder 5)
      - Philippines- Series V, undated (Box 190, Folder 6)
      - Philippines- Series VI, (Irregular), undated (Box 190, Folder 7)
      - Philippines- Labeled Photos, undated (Box 190, Folder 8)
      - Philippines- 7801 (Unlabeled), undated (Box 190, Folder 9)
      - Philippines- Series III and IV, undated (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous (1 Series, 4 Envelopes), undated (Box 190, Folder 11)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous and Ricefields, undated (Box 190, Folder 12)
      - Philippines- People (with Notes), 1930-1937 (Box 190, Folder 13)
      - Philippines- Series 14, 1950 (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous (One Series, Three Envelopes), undated (Box 191, Folder 2)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous (2 Envelopes), undated (Box 191, Folder 3)
      - Philippines- Sagada, 1956 (Box 191, Folder 4)
      - 2 Boxes of Uncut Photographic Proofs, undated (Box 191, Folder 5)
      - Philippines- Sagada, 1956 (Box 191, Folder 6)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - Philippines-Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 191, Folder 8)
      - American West Landscape- (Unsigned), undated (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Sepia Print- Rice Terraces- (Unsigned), undated (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Man and Rice Terraces [2 Photographs]- (Unsigned), undated (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous [2 Envelopes]- (Unsigned), undated (Box 192, Folder 4)
      - “The Pagan Priests”- (Unsigned), undated (Box 192, Folder 5)
      - Photos taken by Raymond Firth at Santa Clara on Trip to SW for Center, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 6)
      - “Headhunter Remembering”- The Philippines, Sagada Circa 1949-1950, Photo by Fred Eggan, Presented to the University of Chicago Camera Club, 1953 (Box 192, Folder 7)
      - “Old Crooked Toes”- Sagada, The Philippines, circa 1949-1950, Photo by Fred Eggan, Presented to the University of Chicago Camera Club, 1953 (Box 192, Folder 8)
      - Pueblo Wall Art- (Unsigned), undated (Box 192, Folder 9)
      - Totem Pole- (Unsigned), undated (Box 192, Folder 10)
      - Photograph by John K. Chua, Jr. undated (Box 192, Folder 11)
      - Prints by Eduardo Masferré, Bontok, Mountain Province, Philippines, 1949-1950 (Box 192, Folder 12)
      - “Madonna Mexicana”, Valle de Bravo, Mexico, October 1953 [1954] (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Slides
      - Moro, Dansalan [4290-D], Lake Lanao, Market, Town, undated (Box 193, Folder 1)
      - Slides #1-17 for Dr. Eggan, undated (Box 193, Folder 2)
      - Orphan Slides, undated (Box 193, Folder 3)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous Glass and Steel Slides, undated (Box 193, Folder 4)
      - Philippines- Bicol and Dum, undated (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - Philippines- Lanao, Mel’s Spirit Bat (?), undated (Box 193, Folder 6)
      - P.L. Moros- Neduick (?), undated (Box 193, Folder 7)
      - Kalinga, Kankanai, undated (Box 193, Folder 8)
      - Kalinga, undated (Box 193, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous Slides, undated (Box 193, Folder 10)
      - Philippines- Besao, Sagada, undated (Box 193, Folder 11)
      - Philippines- Naga Region (41235), 1958 (Box 193, Folder 12)
      - Sagada- Wedding and Market, (8763-C), undated (Box 193, Folder 13)
      - Mountain Province, Manila (8763-A), undated (Box 193, Folder 14)
      - Manila, Baguio, Mountain Province (4476), undated (Box 193, Folder 15)
      - Sagada (9479-D), undated (Box 193, Folder 16)
      - Sagada (9474-B), undated (Box 193, Folder 17)
      - Sagada (9479-A), undated (Box 193, Folder 18)
      - Philippines- Mountain Province- Sagada (41235), 1958 (Box 193, Folder 19)
      - Sagada (8806), undated (Box 193, Folder 20)
      - Sagada (41235), 1957-1958 (Box 193, Folder 21)
      - Sagada (9583-A), June 1950 (Box 193, Folder 22)
      - Sagada (9583-B), June 1950 (Box 193, Folder 23)
      - Sagada- Rice Harvest (9583-C), June 1950 (Box 193, Folder 24)
      - Sagada (9479-C)- Beguias, Kayeo, undated (Box 193, Folder 25)
      - Philippines- Hingotanan, Naga, Air Views- Central Luzon (41235), undated (Box 193, Folder 26)
      - Philippines (11826), undated (Box 193, Folder 27)
      - Dumaguete (4077-B)- Fishing Village Scenes, undated (Box 193, Folder 28)
      - Sagada (8763-D)- Wedding, Guests, Preparation, Rice Fields, Dancing, undated (Box 193, Folder 29)
      - Upi-Nuro, Tiruray (4290-B)- Market, March 1950 (Box 193, Folder 30)
      - Koronodal, Cotobato (4290-A), Valley, Orchid, Mountains, March 1950 (Box 193, Folder 31)
      - Manila, Dumaguete (4391-A)- Manila, Dumaguete, Cebu…Ruins, undated (Box 193, Folder 32)
      - Mountain Province (3779-A)- Baguio City, Mountain Trail, Chico, Villages, undated (Box 193, Folder 33)
      - Mountain Province (3779-B)- Bontok, Sawoki, Bugnay, undated (Box 193, Folder 34)
      - Sagada (8763-B)- Village, Dap’ay, Priests, Dorothy [Numbering Irregular], undated (Box 193, Folder 35)
      - Philippines- Mountain Province- Sagada (41235), 1958 (Box 193, Folder 36)
      - Moro, Lake Lanao, Tugaya (4290-C)- Brass-Working Village, undated (Box 193, Folder 37)
      - Manila- Ouma Guest- Last Trip, undated (Box 193, Folder 38)
      - _____ Banave (9535-B)- Rice Terraces, Villages, Terraces etc. June 1950 (Box 193, Folder 39)
      - Dumaguete (4077-A), March 1950 (Box 193, Folder 40)
      - Sagada (4979-E)- Beguas, Dancing, undated (Box 193, Folder 41)
      - 2 Boxes of Glass Lantern Slides (Box 194)
      - 1 Box of Kodachrome Glass and Steel Slides (Box 194)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Negatives
      - Shoebox containing 6 protective folders with 4” x 5” negatives and key to negatives. (Box 194)
      - Manila Boat, undated (Box 195, Folder 1)
      - Trip Home, Hong Kong, undated (Box 195, Folder 2)
      - Map Negatives, undated (Box 195, Folder 3)
      - Malaysia [4” x 5” Negatives], undated (Box 195, Folder 4)
      - Malaysia [2 Glass Negatives], undated (Box 195, Folder 5)
      - Abra (Tinggian), undated (Box 195, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 195, Folder 7)
      - Tublay, undated (Box 195, Folder 8)
      - Lake Taál, undated (Box 195, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 195, Folder 10)
      - Negrito (Fort Stotsenberg), undated (Box 195, Folder 11)
      - Philippines- Miscellaneous, Unlabeled, undated (Box 195, Folder 12)
      - Sagada- Views, Coffins in Caves, undated (Box 195, Folder 13)
      - Mindanao, Koronadal Valley, undated (Box 195, Folder 14)
      - Negros- Trip to Interior- Bukionons, undated (Box 195, Folder 15)
      - Sagada- Begnas Ceremony, undated (Box 195, Folder 16)
      - Sagada- Village, undated (Box 195, Folder 17)
      - Becky Scenes, undated (Box 195, Folder 18)
      - Sagada, Ceremony, undated (Box 195, Folder 19)
      - Dumaguete- Coconut Groves, undated (Box 195, Folder 20)
      - Mindanao, Agricultural Exhibition, Maramag- Trip, undated (Box 195, Folder 21)
      - Mindanao, Koronadal Resettlement Project, undated (Box 195, Folder 22)
      - Dumaguete- Trip to Interior, Silliman Campus, undated (Box 195, Folder 23)
      - Sagada, Terraces and Rice Fields, undated (Box 195, Folder 24)
      - Mindanao, Davao, undated (Box 195, Folder 25)
      - Baguio (Dumaguete?), undated (Box 195, Folder 26)
      - Sagada, Dapae Village, undated (Box 195, Folder 27)
      - Sagada, undated (Box 195, Folder 28)
      - Sagada, Back Basket, Church, Views, undated (Box 195, Folder 29)
      - Sagada, Church Services, undated (Box 195, Folder 30)
      - Sagada, Dancing, Weaving, Wedding, undated (Box 195, Folder 31)
      - Sagada, Church Services, undated (Box 195, Folder 32)
      - Sagada, Rice Fields, Church, Views, undated (Box 195, Folder 33)
      - Sagada, Dancing, undated (Box 195, Folder 34)
      - Sagada, Begnas Ceremony, undated (Box 195, Folder 35)
      - Sagada, Village, undated (Box 195, Folder 36)
      - Sagada, Village, Carved Coffin Top, undated (Box 195, Folder 37)
      - Sagada, Village, undated (Box 195, Folder 38)
      - Sagada, Views, undated (Box 195, Folder 39)
  - Subseries 9: Restricted
    - University of Chicago appointment and retirement documents, 1932-1973 (Box 196, Folder 1-2)
    - Personal financial material, 1980-1988 (Box 196, Folder 3-14)